{
    "subject": "resource/Tangren_Media",
    "predicate": "property/location",
    "object": "Yichang Road, Shanghai, China",
    "human_readable": "Tangren Media is located at Yichang Road, Shanghai, China.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9731637239456177,
            "question": "Where in Shanghai is Tangren Media situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.919226884841919,
            "question": "Where is Tangren Media located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.90766841173172,
            "question": "In which country is Tangren Media situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9019101858139038,
            "question": "Is Tangren Media in Asia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8472952246665955,
            "question": "On what road is Tangren Media found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.75025874376297,
            "question": "Is Tangren Media located in a major city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6878721714019775,
            "question": "What city is home to Tangren Media?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6866072416305542,
            "question": "What type of company might be found at Yichang Road, Shanghai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6851592659950256,
            "question": "What is the full address of Tangren Media?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6366776823997498,
            "question": "Can you provide the address of Tangren Media?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tangren Media is located at Yichang Road, Shanghai, China.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6191_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the full address of Tangren Media?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6191_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of company might be found at Yichang Road, Shanghai?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6191_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is home to Tangren Media?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6191_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6191_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6191_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6191_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6191_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6191_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6191_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6191_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6191_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6191_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6191_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation for the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the documents mention Tangren Media being located at Yichang Road, Shanghai, China. The documents provide information about the company's business scope, its consistency in maintaining high product quality, and its focus on young people between the ages of 15 and 35. However, they do not provide any specific location for the company."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nThe provided context does not mention any specific location of Tangren Media such as Yichang Road, Shanghai, China. The documents discuss Tangren Media's business activities and focus on producing media content but do not provide information about its exact physical location."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Tangren Media's original establishment was in Australia, not China. The context information does not provide any evidence suggesting a current or past location of the company in Shanghai, China.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Tangren Media's location in the provided context information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Tangren Media being located at Yichang Road, Shanghai, China.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention the location of Tangren Media. Furthermore, the provided details focus on Tangren Cultural Film Group's operations in Australia and its expansion plans for North America, without any reference to a location in Yichang Road, Shanghai, China.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}